<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on My Classroom Analytics</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on My Classroom Analytics</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>For Your Classroom</title>
      <link>/post/first/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:29 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/first/</guid>
      <description>Our dashboard is designed for quick access to meaningful information for your class. We want to allow you to access classroom data in a quick and meaningful way. The My Classroom Analytics Dashboard tool is works easily with Google Classroom &amp;reg;. Data can be exported from Google Classroom &amp;reg; and imported into the dashboard tool where you can quickly view your students&amp;rsquo; information with easy to understand data visualizations and information boxes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ease of Use</title>
      <link>/post/second/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:08:45 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/second/</guid>
      <description>Different tabs in the dashboard provide a variety of ways to view your students&amp;rsquo; information. For classes using differentiated learning methods, the dashboard provides an easy way to determine different groups based on the information imported into the dashboard.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Helpful information from small data</title>
      <link>/post/third/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 14:53:21 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/post/third/</guid>
      <description>Multiple tests, terms, or grades can be used to track students&amp;rsquo; progress over time and see their growth in comparison to their classmates.
Our hope is that your classroom can become a place where your small data can be used to have big impacts on how your students&amp;rsquo; progress can be understood.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>